Dick Clark Papers
Dick Clark Papers
- Recordings, Rock, Roll and Remember (RRR)
  - Show #121, June 2-3, 1984; 5 tapes (Oversize 222)
    Artist: B J Thomas
  - Show #122, June 9-10, 1984; 5 tapes (Oversize 223)
    Year/source: 1973 (T/LP)
  - Show #123, June 16-17, 1984; 5 tapes (Oversize 223)
    Artist: Pat Boone
  - Show #124, June 23-24, 1984; 5 tapes (Oversize 223-224)
    Year/source: 1972 (T/LP)
    Artist: Ray Charles
  - Show #125, Jun 30-July 1, 1984; 5 tapes (Oversize 224)
    Year/source: 1977 (T/LP)
    Artist: Four Tops
  - Show #126, July 7-8, 1984; 5 tapes (Oversize 224)
    Year/source: 1961 (T)
  - Show #127, July 14-15, 1984; 5 tapes (Oversize 224-225)
    Artist: Creedence Clearwater Revival
  - Show #128, July 21-22, 1984; 5 tapes (Oversize 225)
    Year/source: 1969 (T)
    Artist: Tom Jones
  - Show #129, July 28-29, 1984; 5 tapes (Oversize 225-226)
    Artist: Three Dog Night
  - Show #130, August 4-5, 1984; 5 tapes (Oversize 226)
    Artist: Tommy James & the Shondells
  - Show #131, August 11-12, 1984; 5 tapes (Oversize 226)
    Artist: Spinners
  - Show #132, August 18-19, 1984; 5 tapes (Oversize 226-227)
    Artist: Herman’s Hermits
  - Show #133, August 25-26, 1984; 5 tapes (Oversize 227)
    Year/source: 1970 (T)
    Artist: Animals
  - Show #134, Sept 1-2, 1984; 5 tapes (Oversize 227)
  - Show #135, Sept 8-9, 1984; 5 tapes (Oversize 228)
    Artist: O’Jays
  - Show #136, Sept 15-16, 1984; 5 tapes (Oversize 228)
  - Show #137, Sept 22-23, 1984; 5 tapes (Oversize 228-229)
    Artist: Shirelles
  - Show #138, Sept 29-30, 1984; 5 tapes (Oversize 229)
  - Show #139, Oct 7-8, 1984; 5 tapes (Oversize 229)
    Year/source: 1976 (T)
    Artist: Jay & the Americans
  - Show #140, Oct 14-15, 1984; 5 tapes (Oversize 229-230)
    Year/source: 1978 (T/LP)
    Artist: Sly & the Family Stone
  - Show #141, Oct 21-22, 1984; 5 tapes (Oversize 230)
  - Show #142, Oct 28-29, 1984; 5 tapes (Oversize 230-231)
    Year/source: 1957 (T)
  - Show #143, Nov 3-4, 1984; 5 tapes (Oversize 231)
    Artist: Everly Brothers
  - Show #144, Nov 10-11, 1984; 5 tapes (Oversize 231)
    Year/source: 1973 (T)
    Artist: Chubby Checker
  - Show #145, Nov 17-18, 1984; 5 tapes (Oversize 231-232)
  - Show #146, Nov 24-25, 1984; 5 tapes (Oversize 232)
    Artist: Jan & Dean
  - Show #147, Dec 1-2, 1984; 5 tapes (Oversize 232)
    Artist: Herb Alpert & the Tijuana Brass
  - Show #148, Dec 8-9, 1984; 5 tapes (Oversize 233)
  - Show #149, Dec 15-16, 1984; 5 tapes (Oversize 233)
    Artist: Earth Wind & Fire
  - Show #150, Dec 22-23, 1984; 5 tapes (Oversize 233-234)
    Year/source: 1984 (T)
    Artist: RRR Christmas Show
  - Show #151, Dec 29-30, 1984; 5 tapes (Oversize 234)
    Year/source:
    Artist:
  - Show #152, Jan 5-6, 1985; 5 tapes (Oversize 234)
    Year/source: No Year (T)
    Artist: Elvis Presley
  - Show #153, Jan 12-13, 1985; 5 tapes (Oversize 235)
    Artist: Electric Light Orchestra
  - Show #154, Jan 19-20, 1985; 5 tapes (Oversize 235)
    Artist: Donovan
  - Show #155, Jan 26-27, 1985; 5 tapes (Oversize 235-236)
  - Show #156, Feb 2-3, 1985; 5 tapes (Oversize 236)
    Artist: Martha & the Vandellas
  - Show #157, Feb 9-10, 1985; 5 tapes (Oversize 236)
    Artist: Bobby Vee
  - Show #158, Feb 16-17, 1985; 5 tapes (Oversize 236-237)
    Year/source: 1971 (T)
    Artist: Byrds
  - Show #159, Feb 23-24, 1985; 5 tapes (Oversize 237)
    Artist: Four Seasons
  - Show #160, March 2-3, 1985; 5 tapes (Oversize 237-238)
    Artist: Johhny Rivers
  - Show #161, March 9-10, 1985; 5 tapes (Oversize 238)
    Year/source: 1964 (T)
    Artist: Bobby Vinton
  - Show #162, March 16-17, 1985; 5 tapes (Oversize 238)
    Year/source: 1963 (T)
    Artist: Grass Roots
  - Show #163, March 23-24, 1985; 5 tapes (Oversize 238-239)
  - Show #164, March 30-31, 1985; 5 tapes (Oversize 239)
    Artist: Little Anthony & the Imperials
  - Show #165, April 6-7, 1985; 5 tapes (Oversize 239)
    Artist: Steve Miller Band
  - Show #166, April 13-14, 1985; 5 tapes (Oversize 240)
    Year/source: 1980 (T/LP)
    Artist: Doors
  - Show #167, April 20-21, 1985; 5 tapes (Oversize 240)
    Artist: Miracles
  - Show #168, April 27-28, 1985; 5 tapes (Oversize 240-241)
  - Show #169, May 4-5, 1985; 5 tapes (Oversize 241)
    Artist: Mamas & the Papas
  - Show #170, May 11-12, 1985; 5 tapes (Oversize 241)
  - Show #171, May 18-19, 1985; 5 tapes (Oversize 241-242)
  - Show #172, May 25-26, 1985; 5 tapes (Oversize 242)
  - Show #173, June 1-2, 1985; 5 tapes (Oversize 242-243)
  - Show #174, June 8-9, 1985; 5 tapes (Oversize 243)
    Artist: Helen Reddy
  - Show #175, June 15-16, 1985; 5 tapes (Oversize 243)
    Artist: ABBA
  - Show #176, June 22-23, 1985; 5 tapes (Oversize 243-244)
    Year/source: 1968 (T/LP)
    Artist: Al Green
  - Show #177, June 29-30, 1985; 5 tapes (Oversize 244)
    Artist: Johnny Mathis
  - Show #178, July 6-7, 1985; 5 tapes (Oversize 244)
    Artist: Ricky Nelson
  - Show #179, July 13-14, 1985; 5 tapes (Oversize 245)
    Artist: Gary Lewis & the Playboys
  - Show #180, July 20-21, 1985; 5 tapes (Oversize 245)
    Year/source: 1979 (T/LP)
    Artist: Kinks
  - Show #181, July 27-28, 1985; 5 tapes (Oversize 245-246)
    Artist: Jerry Butler
  - Show #182, August 3-4, 1985; 5 tapes (Oversize 246)
  - Show #183, August 10-11, 1985; 5 tapes (Oversize 246)
    Artist: Tommy Roe
  - Show #184, August 17-18, 1985; 5 tapes (Oversize 246-247)
    Artist: Rascals
  - Show #185, August 24-25, 1985; 5 tapes (Oversize 247)
  - Show #186, Aug 31-Sept 1, 1985; 5 tapes (Oversize 247-248)
    Year/source: 1960 (T)
  - Show #187, Sept 7-8, 1985; 5 tapes (Oversize 248)
  - Show #188, Sept 14-15, 1985; 5 tapes (Oversize 248)
    Artist: Lovin’ Spoonful
  - Show #189, Sept 21-22, 1985; 5 tapes (Oversize 248-249)
    Artist: Who
  - Show #190, Sept 28-29, 1985; 5 tapes (Oversize 249)
    Artist: Hollies
  - Show #191, Oct 5-6, 1985; 5 tapes (Oversize 249)
  - Show #192, Oct 12-13, 1985; 5 tapes (Oversize 250)
  - Show #193, Oct 19-20, 1985; 5 tapes (Oversize 250)
    Year/source: 1977 (M)
    Artist: Guess Who
  - Show #194, Oct 26-27, 1985; 5 tapes (Oversize 250-251)
    Year/source: 1971 (M)
    Artist: Simon & Garfunkel
  - Show #195, Nov 2-3, 1985; 5 tapes (Oversize 251)
    Artist: Turtles
  - Show #196, Nov 9-10, 1985; 5 tapes (Oversize 251)
    Year/source: 1974 (T)
    Artist: Sonny & Cher
  - Show #197, Nov 16-17, 1985; 5 tapes (Oversize 251-252)
  - Show #198, Nov 23-24, 1985; 5 tapes (Oversize 252)
  - Show #199, Nov 30-Dec 1, 1985; 5 tapes (Oversize 252-253)
    Year/source: 1979 (T)
  - Show #200, Dec 7-8, 1985; 5 tapes (Oversize 253)
    Year/source: 1956 (T)
  - Show #201, Dec 14-15, 1985; 5 tapes (Oversize 253)
  - Show #202, Dec 21-22, 1985; 5 tapes (Oversize 253-254)
    Year/source: 1985 (T)
  - Show #203, Dec 28-29, 1985; 5 tapes (Oversize 254)
  - Show #204, Jan 4-5, 1986; 5 tapes (Oversize 254)
  - Show #205, Jan 11-12, 1986; 5 tapes (Oversize 255)
  - Show #206, Jan 18-19, 1986; 5 tapes (Oversize 255)
    Year/source: 1959 (T)
  - Show #207, Jan 25-26, 1986; 5 tapes (Oversize 255-256)
    Artist: Jackson Five
  - Show #208, Feb 1-2, 1986; 5 tapes (Oversize 256)
    Year/source: 1966 (T)
    Artist: Brenda Lee
  - Show #209, Feb 8-9, 1986; 5 tapes (Oversize 256)
  - Show #210, Feb 15-16, 1986; 5 tapes (Oversize 256-257)
  - Show #211, Feb 22-23, 1986; 5 tapes (Oversize 257)
    Artist: Crosby, Stills, & Nash
  - Show #212, March 1-2, 1986; 5 tapes (Oversize 257-258)
  - Show #213, March 8-9, 1986; 5 tapes (Oversize 258)
  - Show #214, March 15-16, 1986; 5 tapes (Oversize 258)
    Year/source: 1965 (T)
  - Show #215, March 22-23, 1986; 5 tapes (Oversize 258-259)
  - Show #216, March 29-30, 1986; 5 tapes (Oversize 259)
  - Show #217, April 5-6, 1986; 5 tapes (Oversize 259)
  - Show #218, April 12-13, 1986; 5 tapes (Oversize 260)
    Year/source: 1977 (T)
  - Show #219, April 19-20, 1986; 5 tapes (Oversize 260)
  - Show #220, April 26-27, 1986; 5 tapes (Oversize 260-261)
  - Show #221, May 3-4, 1986; 5 tapes (Oversize 261)
  - Show #222, May 10-11, 1986; 5 tapes (Oversize 261)
  - Show #223, May 17-18, 1986; 5 tapes (Oversize 261-262)
    Year/source: 1981 (T)
    Artist: Bobby Rydell
  - Show #224, May 24-25, 1986; 5 tapes (Oversize 262)
  - Show #225, May 31-Jun 1, 1986; 5 tapes (Oversize 262-263)
  - Show #226, June 7-8, 1986; 5 tapes (Oversize 263)
    Year/source: 1978 (T)
    Artist: Roy Orbison
  - Show #227, June 14-15, 1986; 5 tapes (Oversize 263)
  - Show #228, June 21-22, 1986; 5 tapes (Oversize 263-264)
  - Show #229, June 28-29, 1986; 5 tapes (Oversize 264)
    Year/source: 1980 (T)
  - Show #230, July 5-6, 1986; 5 tapes (Oversize 264)
  - Show #231, July 12-13, 1986; 5 tapes (Oversize 265)
  - Show #232, July 19-20, 1986; 5 tapes (Oversize 265)
  - Show #233, July 26-27, 1986; 5 tapes (Oversize 265-266)
    Year/source: 1962 (T)
  - Show #234, August 2-3, 1986; 5 tapes (Oversize 266)
  - Show #235, August 9-10, 1986; 5 tapes (Oversize 266)
    Year/source: 1967 (T)
  - Show #236, August 16-17, 1986; 5 tapes (Oversize 266-267)
    Artist: Dion
  - Show #237, August 23-24, 1986; 5 tapes (Oversize 267)
  - Show #238, August 30-31, 1986; 5 tapes (Oversize 267-268)
  - Show #239, Sept 6-7, 1986; 5 tapes (Oversize 268)
  - Show #240, Sept 13-14, 1986; 5 tapes (Oversize 268)
  - Show #241, Sept 20-21, 1986; 5 tapes (Oversize 268-269)
  - Show #242, Sept 27-28, 1986; 5 tapes (Oversize 269)
  - Show #243, Oct 4-5, 1986; 5 tapes (Oversize 269)
  - Show #244, Oct 11-12, 1986; 5 tapes (Oversize 270)
    Year/source: 1958 (T)
    Artist: Pointer Sisters
  - Show #245, Oct 18-19, 1986; 5 tapes (Oversize 270)
  - Show #246, Oct 25-26, 1986; 5 tapes (Oversize 270-271)
  - Show #247, Nov 1-2, 1986; 5 tapes (Oversize 271)
  - Show #248, Nov 8-9, 1986; 5 tapes (Oversize 271)
  - Show #249, Nov 15-16, 1986; 5 tapes (Oversize 272)
  - Show #250, Nov 22-23, 1986; 5 tapes (Oversize 272)
  - Show #251, Nov 29-30, 1986; 5 tapes (Oversize 272-273)
  - Show #252, Dec 6-7, 1986; 5 tapes (Oversize 273)
    Artist: Dave Clark Five
  - Show #253, Dec 13-14, 1986; 5 tapes (Oversize 273)
  - Show #254, Dec 20-21, 1986; 5 tapes (Oversize 273-274)
    Year/source: 1986 (T)
  - Show #255, Dec 27-28, 1986; 5 tapes (Oversize 274)
  - Show #256, Jan 3-4, 1987; 5 tapes (Oversize 274)
  - Show #257, Jan 10-11, 1987; 5 tapes (Oversize 275)
    Artist: Johnny Rivers
  - Show #258, Jan 17-18, 1987; 5 tapes (Oversize 275)
    Artist: Earth, Wind & Fire
  - Show #259, Jan 24-25, 1987; 5 tapes (Oversize 275-276)
  - Show #260, Jan 31-Feb 1, 1987; 5 tapes (Oversize 276)
  - Show #261, Feb 7-8, 1987; 5 tapes (Oversize 276)
  - Show #262, Feb 14-15, 1987; 5 tapes (Oversize 276-277)
    Artist: Drifters
  - Show #263, Feb 21-22, 1987; 5 tapes (Oversize 277)
    Artist: Rick Nelson
  - Show #264, Feb 28-Mar 1, 1987; 5 tapes (Oversize 277-278)
    Artist: Fifth Dimension
  - Show #265, March 7-8, 1987; 5 tapes (Oversize 278)
  - Show #266, March 14-15, 1987; 5 tapes (Oversize 278)
  - Show #267, March 21-22, 1987; 5 tapes (Oversize 278-279)
  - Show #268, March 28-29, 1987; 5 tapes (Oversize 279)
  - Show #269, April 4-5, 1987; 5 tapes (Oversize 279)
  - Show #270, April 11-12, 1987; 5 tapes (Oversize 280)
  - Show #271, April 18-19, 1987; 5 tapes (Oversize 280)
  - Show #272, April 25-26, 1987; 5 tapes (Oversize 280-281)
  - Show #273, May 2-3, 1987; 5 tapes (Oversize 281)
  - Show #274, May 9-10, 1987; 5 tapes (Oversize 281)
  - Show #275, May 16-17, 1987; 5 tapes (Oversize 281-282)
    Artist: Bobby Darin
  - Show #276, May 23-24, 1987; 5 tapes (Oversize 282)
  - Show #277, May 30-31, 1987; 5 tapes (Oversize 282-283)
  - Show #278, June 6-7, 1987; 5 tapes (Oversize 283)
  - Show #279, June 13-14, 1987; 5 tapes (Oversize 283)
  - Show #280, June 20-21, 1987; 5 tapes (Oversize 283-284)
  - Show #281, June 27-28, 1987; 5 tapes (Oversize 284)
  - Show #282, July 4-5, 1987; 5 tapes (Oversize 284)
  - Show #283, July 11-12, 1987; 5 tapes (Oversize 285)
  - Show #284, July 18-19, 1987; 5 tapes (Oversize 285)
    Artist: Jefferson Airplane
  - Show #285, July 25-26, 1987; 5 tapes (Oversize 285-286)
  - Show #286, August 1-2, 1987; 5 tapes (Oversize 286)
  - Show #287, August 8-9, 1987; 5 tapes (Oversize 286)
  - Show #288, August 15-16, 1987; 5 tapes (Oversize 286-287)
  - Show #289, August 22-23, 1987; 5 tapes (Oversize 287)
  - Show #290, August 29-30, 1987; 5 tapes (Oversize 287-288)
  - Show #291, Sept 5-6, 1987; 5 tapes (Oversize 288)
    Artist: Buddy Holly
  - Show #292, Sept 12-13, 1987; 5 tapes (Oversize 288)
    Year/source: 1966 (LP)
    Artist: Dion & the Belmonts
  - Show #293, Sept 19-20, 1987; 5 tapes (Oversize 288-289)
  - Show #294, Sept 26-27, 1987; 5 tapes (Oversize 289)
    Artist: Del Shannon
  - Show #295, Oct 3-4, 1987; 5 tapes (Oversize 289)
  - Show #296, Oct 10-11, 1987; 5 tapes (Oversize 290)
  - Show #297, Oct 17-18, 1987; 5 tapes (Oversize 290)
  - Show #298, Oct 24-25, 1987; 5 tapes (Oversize 290-291)
  - Show #299, Oct 31-Nov 1, 1987; 5 tapes (Oversize 291)
  - Show #300, Nov 7-8, 1987; 5 tapes (Oversize 291)
  - Show #301, Nov 14-15, 1987; 5 tapes (Oversize 291-292)
  - Show #302, Nov 21-22, 1987; 5 tapes (Oversize 292)
  - Show #303, Nov 28-29, 1987; 5 tapes (Oversize 292-293)
  - Show #304, Dec 5-6, 1987; 5 tapes (Oversize 293)
    Artist: Peter & Gordon
  - Show #305, Dec 12-13, 1987; 5 tapes (Oversize 293)
  - Show #306, Dec 19-20, 1987; 5 tapes (Oversize 293-294)
    Year/source: 1987 (T/LP)
  - Show #307, Dec 26-27, 1987; 5 tapes (Oversize 294)
  - Show #308, Jan 2-3, 1988; 5 tapes (Oversize 294)
  - Show #309, Jan 9-10, 1988; 5 tapes (Oversize 295)
  - Show #310, Jan 16-17, 1988; 5 tapes (Oversize 295)
  - Show #311, Jan 23-24, 1988; 5 tapes (Oversize 295-296)
  - Show #312, Jan 30-31, 1988; 5 tapes (Oversize 296)
    Artist: Platters
  - Show #313, Feb 6-7, 1988; 5 tapes (Oversize 296)
  - Show #314, Feb 13-14, 1988; 5 tapes (Oversize 296-297)
    Artist: Love Songs Special
  - Show #315, Feb 20-21, 1988; 5 tapes (Oversize 297)
  - Show #316, Feb 27-28, 1988; 5 tapes (Oversize 297-298)
  - Show #317, March 5-6, 1988; 5 tapes (Oversize 298)
  - Show #318, March 12-13, 1988; 5 tapes (Oversize 298)
  - Show #319, March 19-20, 1988; 5 tapes (Oversize 298-299)
  - Show #320, March 26-27, 1988; 5 tapes (Oversize 299)
  - Show #321, April 2-3, 1988; 5 tapes (Oversize 299)
  - Show #322, April 9-10, 1988; 5 tapes (Oversize 300)
  - Show #323, April 16-17, 1988; 5 tapes (Oversize 300)
  - Show #324, April 23-24, 1988; 5 tapes (Oversize 300-301)
    Artist: Paul Anka
  - Show #325, Apr 30-May 1, 1988; 5 tapes (Oversize 301)
    Artist: Crosby, Stills & Nash
  - Show #326, May 7-8, 1988; 5 tapes (Oversize 301)
  - Show #327, May 14-15, 1988; 5 tapes (Oversize 301-302)
  - Show #328, May 21-22, 1988; 5 tapes (Oversize 302)
  - Show #329, May 28-29, 1988; 5 tapes (Oversize 302-303)
    Artist: Neil Sedaka
  - Show #330, June 4-5, 1988; 5 tapes (Oversize 303)
  - Show #331, June 11-12, 1988; 5 tapes (Oversize 303)
  - Show #332, June 18-19, 1988; 5 tapes (Oversize 303-304)
    Artist: Dusty Springfield
  - Show #333, June 25-26, 1988; 5 tapes (Oversize 304)
    Artist: Beatles
  - Show #334, July 2-3, 1988; 5 tapes (Oversize 304)
  - Show #335, July 9-10, 1988; 5 tapes (Oversize 305)
  - Show #336, July 16-17, 1988; 5 tapes (Oversize 305)
    Artist: Lesley Gore
  - Show #337, July 23-24, 1988; 5 tapes (Oversize 305-306)
    Artist: Gene Pitney
  - Show #338, July 30-31, 1988; 5 tapes (Oversize 306)
  - Show #339, August 6-7, 1988; 5 tapes (Oversize 306)
    Artist: Glen Campbell
  - Show #340, August 13-14, 1988; 5 tapes (Oversize 306-307)
  - Show #341, August 20-21, 1988; 5 tapes (Oversize 307)
  - Show #342, August 27-28, 1988; 5 tapes (Oversize 307-308)
  - Show #343, Sept 3-4, 1988; 5 tapes (Oversize 308)
  - Show #345, Sept 17-18, 1988; 5 tapes (Oversize 308-309)
  - Show #346, Sept 24-25, 1988; 5 tapes (Oversize 309)
  - Show #347, Oct 1-2, 1988; 5 tapes (Oversize 309)
  - Show #348, Oct 8-9, 1988; 5 tapes (Oversize 310)
  - Show #349, Oct 15-16, 1988; 5 tapes (Oversize 310)
  - Show #350, Oct 22-23, 1988; 5 tapes (Oversize 310-311)
  - Show #351, Oct 29-30, 1988; 5 tapes (Oversize 311)
    Artist: Do Wop Special
  - Show #352, Nov 5-6, 1988; 5 tapes (Oversize 311)
    Artist: Chuck Berry
  - Show #353, Nov 12-13, 1988; 5 tapes (Oversize 311-312)
  - Show #354, Nov 19-20, 1988; 5 tapes (Oversize 312)
  - Show #355, Nov 26-27, 1988; 5 tapes (Oversize 312-313)
  - Show #356, Dec 3-4, 1988; 5 tapes (Oversize 313)
  - Show #357, Dec 10-11, 1988; 5 tapes (Oversize 313)
    Year/source: 1972 (LP)
  - Show #358, Dec 17-18, 1988; 5 tapes (Oversize 313-314)
    Year/source: 1961 (LP)
  - Show #359, Dec 24-25, 1988; 5 tapes (Oversize 314)
    Year/source: 1988 (T/LP)
  - Show #360, Dec 31-Jan 1, 1989; 5 tapes (Oversize 314)
  - Show #361, Jan 7-8, 1989; 5 tapes (Oversize 315)
  - Show #362, Jan 14-15, 1989; 5 tapes (Oversize 315)
  - Show #363, Jan 21-22, 1989; 5 tapes (Oversize 315-316)
  - Show #364, Jan 28-29, 1989; 5 tapes (Oversize 316)
  - Show #365, Feb 4-5, 1989; 5 tapes (Oversize 316)
  - Show #366, Feb 11-12, 1989; 4 tapes (Oversize 316-317)
    There is no 366E. Original shipment contained only A-D.
  - Show #367, Feb 18-19, 1989; 5 tapes (Oversize 317)
    Year/source: 1968 (LP)
    Artist: Girl Groups
  - Show #368, Feb 25-26, 1989; 5 tapes (Oversize 317-318)
    Year/source: 1976 (LP)
  - Show #369, March 4-5, 1989; 5 tapes (Oversize 318)
    Year/source: 1977 (LP)
  - Show #370, March 11-12, 1989; 5 tapes (Oversize 318)
    Year/source: 1965 (LP)
  - Show #371, March 18-19, 1989; 5 tapes (Oversize 318-319)
  - Show #372, March 25-26, 1989; 5 tapes (Oversize 319)
  - Show #373, April 1-2, 1989; 5 tapes (Oversize 319)
  - Show #374, April 8-9, 1989; 5 tapes (Oversize 320)
    Year/source: 1963 (LP)
    Artist: Jr Walker
  - Show #375, April 15-16, 1989; 5 tapes (Oversize 320)
    Year/source: 1958 (LP)
  - Show #376, April 22-23, 1989; 5 tapes (Oversize 320-321)
    Year/source: 1970 (LP)
  - Show #377, April 29-30, 1989; 5 tapes (Oversize 321)
    Year/source: 1959 (LP)
  - Show #378, May 6-7, 1989; 5 tapes (Oversize 321)
  - Show #379, May 13-14, 1989; 5 tapes (Oversize 321-322)
  - Show #380, May 20-21, 1989; 5 tapes (Oversize 322)
  - Show #381, May 27-28, 1989; 5 tapes (Oversize 322-323)
  - Show #382, June 3-4, 1989; 5 tapes (Oversize 323)
  - Show #384, June 17-18, 1989; 5 tapes (Oversize 323-324)
    Year/source: 1973 (LP)
  - Show #385, June 24-25, 1989; 5 tapes (Oversize 324)
  - Show #386, July 1-2, 1989; 5 tapes (Oversize 324)
  - Show #387, July 8-9, 1989; 5 tapes (Oversize 325)
    Year/source: 1968 (M)
  - Show #388, July 15-16, 1989; 5 tapes (Oversize 325)
    Year/source: 1957 (LP)
  - Show #389, July 22-23, 1989; 5 tapes (Oversize 325-326)
    Year/source: 1965 (M)
    Artist: Connie Francis
  - Show #390, July 29-30, 1989; 5 tapes (Oversize 326)
    Year/source: 1969 (M)
    Artist: Ringo Starr
  - Show #391, August 5-6, 1989; 5 tapes (Oversize 326)
  - Show #392, August 12-13, 1989; 5 tapes (Oversize 326-327)
  - Show #393, August 19-20, 1989; 5 tapes (Oversize 327)
    Artist: Petula Clark
  - Show #394, August 26-27, 1989; 5 tapes (Oversize 327-328)
  - Show #397, Sept 16-17, 1989; 5 tapes (Oversize 328)
  - Show #398, Sept 23-24, 1989; 5 tapes (Oversize 328)
  - Show #399, Sept 30-Oct 1, 1989; 5 tapes (Oversize 328-329)
    Year/source: 1974 (LP)
  - Show #400, Oct 7-8, 1989; 5 tapes (Oversize 329)
  - Show #401, Oct 14-15, 1989; 5 tapes (Oversize 329)
  - Show #402, Oct 21-22, 1989; 5 tapes (Oversize 330)
  - Show #403, Oct 28-29, 1989; 5 tapes (Oversize 330)
  - Show #404, Nov 4-5, 1989; 5 tapes (Oversize 330-331)
  - Show #405, Nov 11-12, 1989; 5 tapes (Oversize 331)
  - Show #406, Nov 18-19, 1989; 5 tapes (Oversize 331)
  - Show #407, Nov 25-26, 1989; 5 tapes (Oversize 331-332)
  - Show #408, Dec 2-3, 1989; 5 tapes (Oversize 332)
  - Show #409, Dec 9-10, 1989; 5 tapes (Oversize 332-333)
  - Show #410, Dec 16-17, 1989; 5 tapes (Oversize 333)
  - Show #411, Dec 23-24, 1989; 5 tapes (Oversize 333)
    Year/source: 1989 (T/LP)
  - Show #412, Dec 30-31, 1989; 5 tapes (Oversize 333-334)
  - Show #413, Jan 6-7, 1990; 5 tapes (Oversize 334)
  - Show #414, Jan 13-14, 1990; 5 tapes (Oversize 334)
  - Show #415, Jan 20-21, 1990; 5 tapes (Oversize 335)
  - Show #416, Jan 27-28, 1990; 5 tapes (Oversize 335)
  - Show #417, Feb 3-4, 1990; 5 tapes (Oversize 335-336)
  - Show #418, Feb 10-11, 1990; 5 tapes (Oversize 336)
  - Show #419, Feb 17-18, 1990; 5 tapes (Oversize 336)
  - Show #420, Feb 24-25, 1990; 5 tapes (Oversize 336-337)
  - Show #421, March 3-4, 1990; 5 tapes (Oversize 337)
  - Show #422, March 10-11, 1990; 5 tapes (Oversize 337-338)
  - Show #425, Mar 31-Apr 1, 1990; 5 tapes (Oversize 338)
  - Show #426, April 7-8, 1990; 5 tapes (Oversize 338)
  - Show #427, April 14-15, 1990; 5 tapes (Oversize 338-339)
  - Show #428, April 21-22, 1990; 5 tapes (Oversize 339)
  - Show #429, April 28-29, 1990; 5 tapes (Oversize 339)
  - Show #430, May 5-6, 1990; 5 tapes (Oversize 340)
  - Show #431, May 12-13, 1990; 5 tapes (Oversize 340)
  - Show #432, May 19-20, 1990; 5 tapes (Oversize 340-341)
  - Show #433, May 26-27, 1990; 5 tapes (Oversize 341)
  - Show #434, June 2-3, 1990; 5 tapes (Oversize 341)
  - Show #435, June 9-10, 1990; 5 tapes (Oversize 341-342)
  - Show #436, June 16-17, 1990; 5 tapes (Oversize 342)
  - Show #437, June 23-24, 1990; 5 tapes (Oversize 343-343)
  - Show #438, June 30-July 1, 1990; 5 tapes (Oversize 343)
  - Show #439, July 7-8, 1990; 5 tapes (Oversize 343)
  - Show #440, July 14-15, 1990; 5 tapes (Oversize 343-344)
  - Show #441, July 21-22, 1990; 5 tapes (Oversize 344)
  - Show #442, July 28-29, 1990; 5 tapes (Oversize 344)
  - Show #443, August 4-5, 1990; 5 tapes (Oversize 345)
  - Show #444, August 11-12, 1990; 5 tapes (Oversize 345)
  - Show #445, August 18-19, 1990; 5 tapes (Oversize 345-346)
  - Show #446, August 25-26, 1990; 5 tapes (Oversize 346)
  - Show #447, Sept 1-2, 1990; 5 tapes (Oversize 346)
  - Show #448, Sept 8-9, 1990; 5 tapes (Oversize 346-347)
  - Show #449, Sept 15-16, 1990; 5 tapes (Oversize 347)
    Year/source: 1969 (LP)
  - Show #450, Sept 22-23, 1990; 5 tapes (Oversize 347-348)
  - Show #451, Sept 29-30, 1990; 5 tapes (Oversize 348)
  - Show #452, Oct 6-7, 1990; 5 tapes (Oversize 348)
  - Show #453, Oct 13-14, 1990; 5 tapes (Oversize 348-349)
  - Show #454, Oct 20-21, 1990; 5 tapes (Oversize 349)
  - Show #455, Oct 27-28, 1990; 5 tapes (Oversize 349)
  - Show #456, Nov 3-4, 1990; 5 tapes (Oversize 350)
  - Show #457, Nov 10-11, 1990; 5 tapes (Oversize 350)
  - Show #458, Nov 17-18, 1990; 5 tapes (Oversize 350-351)
  - Show #459, Nov 24-25, 1990; 5 tapes (Oversize 351)
  - Show #460, Dec 1-2, 1990; 5 tapes (Oversize 351)
  - Show #461, Dec 8-9, 1990; 5 tapes (Oversize 351-352)
    Year/source: 1958 (M)
  - Show #462, Dec 15-16, 1990; 5 tapes (Oversize 352)
    Year/source: 1967 (LP)
  - Show #463, Dec 22-23, 1990; 5 tapes (Oversize 352-353)
    Year/source: 1990 (T/LP)
  - Show #464, Dec 29-30, 1990; 5 tapes (Oversize 353)
  - Show #91-1/465, Jan 5-6, 1991; 5 tapes (Oversize 353)
  - Show #91-2/466, Jan 12-13, 1991; 5 tapes (Oversize 353-354)
  - Show #91-3/467, Jan 19-20, 1991; 5 tapes (Oversize 354)
    Artist: Sam Cooke
  - Show #91-4/468, Jan 26-27, 1991; 5 tapes (Oversize 354)
  - Show #91-5/469, Feb 2-3, 1991; 5 tapes (Oversize 355)
  - Show #91-6/470, Feb 9-10, 1991; 5 tapes (Oversize 355)
  - Show #91-7/471, Feb 16-17, 1991; 5 tapes (Oversize 355-356)
  - Show #91-8/472, Feb 23-24, 1991; 5 tapes (Oversize 356)
  - Show #91-9/473, March 2-3, 1991; 5 tapes (Oversize 356)
  - Show #91-10/474, March 9-10, 1991; 5 tapes (Oversize 356-357)
  - Show #91-11/475, March 16-17, 1991; 5 tapes (Oversize 357)
  - Show #91-12/476, March 23-24, 1991; 5 tapes (Oversize 357)